all right so here's just a quick video
on how I actually turn
a transcript
where you we utilize a tour a tool
called
otter.ai
to transcribe a live training
um from one of my clients and it's
actually it's my mom
uh Sandy Krakowski
for her stocks and crypto group
which is a course grader and coach
what's cool is Jasper actually
recognizes for tone of voice
so I actually put it under tone of voice
which is cool right there
um but all that said
this is a transcript of a conversation
that she had that I want to turn into an
email so I'll do is I'll go
summarize the above
and I found this section of the uh the
training because I thought it would make
a really great email
convert the above to
pas
sensitive information
okay
so that was a glitch so this I'll
summarize
the above once more
let's try it one more time
or PAs copy based on the above
no okay so that gives me water text so
what I end up doing is I end up putting
the three stars
right above this line
and I'm just going to write it based off
of those summaries it's hard to make a
difference in the world it seems like
everything's worked against you it can
be frustrating demoralizing when it
feels you're fighting a pill there's a
way to make it impact you can use your
skills to create wealth
very focused on discipline or anything
is possible
awesome
okay so there's our problem agitate
solution right there then I'll go back
I'll look at this transcript it's about
three thousand words
so I'm going to delete
about that much of it right there
let me do it again summarize the above
summarize the above oh this is It's
finding
marketing language
um based off of what the transcript was
okay
right Pas copy bait
based on the above
okay it's dealing with Lacroix water
copy again
put this right here it'll prevent it
from trying to look above that line
my kitty's crying over here
making money day trading is hard when
people make more money than ever before
they get greedy especially for disaster
discipline is key when day trading okay
so I'm gonna delete one more summarize
the above
is the above
summarize the above
right PS copy based on the above
all right so it's now it's more water
copy
why does it do water copy because
uh it's it's got a glitch and it
glitches out and I don't know why it
doesn't so
it's the case
they're playing around and not taking
them you can make amount of some money
all right
so now we're going to take this we're
going to say write a creative story
based on the above
so now I'm going to put this just the
other day
I was
I was watching
the Netflix special
it's actually called
it's called The Bridge
that's right
to the Moon
Netflix special Eat the Rich
the GameStop Saga
I was reminded of
of why you need to be disciplined in
this stock market
what I mean is it's so easy to get
caught off guard and hype to make
impulse decisions that can lead to you
losing everything you worked hard for
I'm not saying it's scary to remind you
that greed is a very real thing
and it can destroy even the most
disciplined investors
the documentary
which I recommend watching
this as well as
it actually called
which both follow a group of people who
made a killing in the market by simply
following what everyone else was doing
stocks like AMC
and GMA
okay so now I'm going to take this on
this up here
I'm going to have it right
about that information right there
thank you
it's a perfect example I need to not get
caught up
in the frenzy of what the news media
and social media like Reddit
Twitter and Facebook are saying
about investing
some pulses
doing with the right rules
and disciplined
strategy and Order
what
if you want to learn to trade stocks and
they're just starting out
jump
to my stocks
for Joe Academy where we're trading
every day together
in the morning
right as the opening
Bell raise
foreign
hundreds of my students are making
real money
trading stocks
and you can be next okay
perfect
so that's how I basically take a
transcript
pull out the key
elements of it and then use Jasper to
come up with like emails and social
media type posts like that